(Howard:)Then what's with the disinfectant?
(Sheldon:)I know where my feet have been.
(Stuart:)Hey, Penny.
(Stuart:)And you guys.
(Stuart:)Albino Bob couldn't make it,
so I brought a substitute.
(Stuart:)I believe some of you
know Wil Wheaton.
(Wil:)Hi, Sheldon. How's it going?
(Sheldon:)Well, well, well,
if it isn't Wil Wheaton.
(Sheldon:)The Green Goblin to my Spider-Man.
The Pope Paul V to my Galileo.
(Sheldon:)The Internet Explorer to my Firefox.
Not carrying a grudge because I beat you
at that card tournament, are you?
(Sheldon:)I'm the proud owner
of Wil-Wheaton-stinks.com...
...dot-net and dot-org.
What does that tell you?
(Wil:)It tells me that I am living rent-free
right here.
(Wil:)-You ready to bowl?
-Oh, I'm ready.
(Sheldon:)I don't know if Stuart told you
what you're up against...
(Sheldon:)...but before you stands the co-captain
of the East Texas Christian Youth...